

# PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

- JavaScript
- HTML/CSS
- Ruby
- Ruby on Rails
- Bootstrap
- Visual Studio
- SQL
- Heroku
- Triva
- Git
- Github
- Webpack
- Node.js

#### **PERSONAL SKILLS**

- Budgeting and Financial
- Problem-solving attitude & Conflict Resolution prone
- Multi-tasking
- Strong work ethic
- Fast learner
- Ability to share knowledge

#### CONTACT

Phone: +44 7394 114367 Email: chi.ferr1188@gmail.com City: London,UK

## SOCIAL

LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/chiaraferrari-1188

Github: ferrari1188

# CHIARA FERRARI

### JUNIOR FULLSTACK DEVELOPER

#### **ABOUT**

I started to code for fun and I couldn't stop. I joined Le Wagon Bootcamp, where I spent 10 intense and exciting weeks learning to code. Now I am looking forward to the next opportunity to continue to grow and challenge myself. I am used to working under pressure and in a fast environment, and I am looking forward to using my skills and knowledge in a new challenging environment.

#### **EDUCATION**

GRADUATE WEB DEVELOPMENT

Bootcamp Le Wagon London 2021 - 2021

CS50 COMPUTER SCIENCE

EdX HardvardX 2021 - currently pursuing

FULL STACK JAVASCRIPT DEVELOPER NANODEGREE

Udacity 2021 - currently pursuing

# **PROJECTS**

#### TREK

https://treking-lewagon.herokuapp.com

Trek is a trekking app that allows you to explore the great outdoors by choosing a route to go to and be able to add notifications along the way.

AIRBNB-CLONE

https://airbnb-benwest0291.herokuapp.com

This app is a marketplace for renting out famous places.

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

STORE MANAGER

Caffè Nero | Feb 2019 - May 2021

- Team management: managing a team of 10. In charge to lead the recruitment process.
- Store supplies management, products daily control, and store inventory management using Crunchtime software.
- Budget management: managing store yearly budget for £560,000.
  Invoices management on Crunchtime. Missing margin control check.
  Financial quarter planning and quarterly business review.
- Customer service, company culture, and brand promotion.

#### CHEF DE PARTIE

Bar Belli Restaurant | Oct 2017 - Jan 2019

- Menu design and food cost responsible.
- Food vendors management.
- Location management: arranging new locations on a daily basis.